mphonline.com 2018-06-29

# MPHONLINE.COM - Malaysia's No. 1 Online Bookstore

MPH Bookstores Sdn Bhd is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. This privacy policy is formulated in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act 2010, which describes how your information is collected and used and your choices with respect to your Personal Data. This policy explains how we use the information we collect about you and the procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy whilst you use the website.

MPH Bookstores Sdn Bhd may disclose to third party service providers within and outside of Malaysia certain aggregate information contained in your registration applications but MPH Bookstores Sdn Bhd will not disclose to any individuals your name, address, email address or telephone number without your prior consent except to the extent necessary or appropriate to comply with applicable laws or in legal proceedings.

**Information collected by MPH Bookstores Sdn Bhd**

MPH Bookstores Sdn Bhd does not sell, share or trade customers personal information collected online with third parties.

Our Web servers do not automatically recognise specific information about individual users on our site. In addition, our servers do not automatically record information regarding a user's e-mail address unless the user supplies it.

We collect information about users during the registration process for certain parts of our site; through their participation in certain activities, including contests, and through the use of cookies.

The user-supplied information collected through the registration process, surveys, contest entry forms or other similar vehicles is used to improve the content of our site, or used for our marketing purposes. It is not shared with other organisations for commercial purposes unless specifically stated.

Although the precise details of the Personal Data collected will vary according to the specific purpose (such as contests, forums, surveys etc) whether via online or otherwise, we may typically collect the following Personal Data from or in relation to you:

  * Name;
  * Address;
  * Phone number(s);
  * Date of birth;
  * Email address;
  * Gender;
  * Identity card number or passport number

**Purpose of Personal Data collected**

Personal Data that you provide to us voluntarily on our website and its other related channels will be processed for the following purposes:

  * to enable you to make purchases at our website;
  * to process exchanges or product returns;
  * for processing of payments and receipts;
  * to enable you to participate in promotions and contests;
  * to improve our services;
  * to respond to requests or complaints;
  * to understand customers’ needs and offering products and services to meet those needs;
  * for purposes of rewarding you through our customer loyalty programs
  * for delivery of communication via SMSes, emails & social media
  * for such other purposes as permitted by applicable law or with your consent; and,
  * for all other purposes incidental and associated with any of the above. 

**Use and Disclosure of your Personal Data**

We may disclose your Personal Data to other subsidiaries within our group. These subsidiaries will treat your Personal Data as confidential, in accordance with this Privacy Policy and with all applicable Data Protection legislation and will process such Personal Data only for the Purposes and within the terms set out herein.

We are responsible for the Personal Data under our control, including Personal Data disclosed by us to a Vendor (often referred to as the data processor). "Vendor" in this Privacy Policy means in relation to Personal Data any person or entity (other than an employee of MPH Bookstores Sdn Bhd) who processes the Personal Data on behalf of us. "Processing", in relation to Personal Data means for example obtaining, recording, holding or using the Personal Data in carrying out any operation or set of operations on the Personal Data including organisation, compilation, retrieval disclosure of the Personal Data for verification Purposes.

We take every measure to provide a comparable level of protection for Personal Data should the information be Processed by a Vendor.

We use and disclose aggregated non-personally identifying information collected through this Website as part of our organisation's process of constantly improving this Website and/or business.

We may also use your contact information to send newsletters via email or short message services (SMS).

**Storage and Retention of Personal Data**

Your Personal Data shall be stored either in hard copies in our offices or stored in servers located in Malaysia and operated by our service providers or us.

We do not offer any online facilities for you to delete your Personal Data held by us.

**Collection of Computer Data**

When you visit MPHONLINE.COM, our company servers will automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This data may include:

  * Your computer's IP address
  * Browser type
  * Webpage you were visiting before you came to our site
  * The pages within MPHONLINE.com you visit
  * The time spent on those pages, items and information searched for on our site, access times and dates, and other statistics.

This information is collected for analysis and evaluation in order to help us improve our site and the services and products we provide. This data will not be used in association with any other personal information.

**Rights to Access, Update & Limit Your Personal Information**

You have the right to request for access to your personal data processed by us on MPHONLINE.com website with reasonable notice.

This also includes request for correction and/or update of your personal data that is inaccurate, incomplete or outdated.

You are also entitled to limit our processing of your personal data by expressly withdrawing in full, your consent given previously, in each case, including for direct marketing purposes subject to any applicable legal restrictions, contractual conditions and within a reasonable time period.

**Registration as a member on MPHONLINE.com website**

When you register as a member on MPHONLINE.com website, we will also use your personal information to send you marketing and/or promotional materials from time to time via email and SMSes. If relevant, we will allow our sister companies to send relevant marketing materials to you. You can unsubscribe from marketing information at any time by using the unsubscribe function within the electronic marketing material.

**Subscribing to MPHONLINE.com e-newsletter**

Upon subscribing to our MPHONLINE.com e-newsletter, you will be receiving marketing and/or promotional emails from us, which includes monthly promotions, new titles, in-store news and etc.

**Unsubscribe the e-newsletter from MPHONLINE.com**

If you wish to unsubscribe our enewsletter, please log on to www.mphonline.com, go to Account setting and click "No" for E-Newsletter option and you will automatically be excluded from any e-newsletters from us. 

If you have any queries about how to unsubscribe our enewsletter, please email us at contact@mph.com.my or contact us at 1300-888-674

Any email that we send to you will also contains an easy automated unsubscribe link so that you can opt-out of the subscription. Simply follow the indications in the email.

**Confidentiality**

Personal Data held by us will be kept confidential in accordance with this Privacy Policy pursuant to any applicable law that may from time to time be in force.

Any questions, comments, suggestions or information other than Personal Data sent or posted to this Website, or any part of the this Website by visitors will be deemed voluntarily provided to us on a non-confidential and non-proprietary basis.  
We reserve the right to use, reproduce, disclose, transmit, publish, broadcast and/or post elsewhere such information freely as set out in (3) above.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice. We advise that you check this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

**Complaints and Disputes**

If you have reason to believe that we have breached the principles set out in this Notice, we urge you to raise this with us. You may contact us via the following channels:

  * contact us via phone at 1300-888-674 ;
  * e-mail us at contact@mph.com.my; or 
  * write to us. Please address the letter to:- MPH BOOKSTORES SDN BHD 3rd Floor, Lot 1 & 2, Bangunan TH No.5, Jalan Bersatu, Section 13/4 46200 Petaling Jaya

We will investigate all complaints and you will usually receive a response within 30 days. If we find a complaint justified, we will resolve it.
